Guide to the Bingham Center Women's Zine Collection, 1992-2017 RL.01406
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession (2006-0136), 1992-2006; 795759; 35 boxes
  - Postmarked Last Wednesday, 796042 (Box 24)
  - Power Candy (2 Folders), 796041 (Box 24)
  - Prevailing Nonsense, 796040 (Box 24)
  - Principles of Anarchism, 796039 (Box 24)
  - Prison, 796038 (Box 24)
  - The Prison Industrial Complex, 796037 (Box 24)
  - Prisoners of a Hard Life, 796036 (Box 24)
  - Prisoner Support, 796035 (Box 24)
  - Prisoners: A Social Crime, 796034 (Box 24)
  - Process, 796033 (Box 24)
  - Producing Concerts, 796032 (Box 24)
  - Prom Queen, 796031 (Box 24)
  - The Propaganda, 796030 (Box 24)
  - Provocative, 796029 (Box 24)
  - Psycho Reality, 796028 (Box 24)
  - Punk Planet (2 Folders), 796027 (Box 24)
  - Push, 796026 (Box 24)
  - Push, 796025 (Box 25)
  - A Queer and Trans Fat Activits Timeline, 796024 (Box 25)
  - Queers Bash Back, 796023 (Box 25)
  - Queer Ramblings, 796022 (Box 25)
  - Queer Zine Explosion, 796021 (Box 25)
  - Que Jodenos Estos, 796020 (Box 25)
  - Qui Riposa, 796019 (Box 25)
  - Quitter Quarterly, 796018 (Box 25)
  - The Rabbit Fodder Addict, 796017 (Box 25)
  - Race Revolt, 796016 (Box 25)
  - Racing Toward Moonlight, 796015 (Box 25)
  - Radicalism, 796014 (Box 25)
  - The Rag (3 Folders), 796013 (Box 25)
  - Ransom Street, 796012 (Box 25)
  - Rape (Riot Grrrl Omaha), 796011 (Box 25)
  - Rats and Wings, 796010 (Box 25)
  - Rat Bat, 796009 (Box 25)
  - Reaching Through the Bars, 796008 (Box 25)
  - Read My Lips: No More Madonna Poems Strikes Back, 796007 (Box 25)
  - Real, 796006 (Box 25)
  - Rebel-a-Go-Go, 796005 (Box 25)
  - Reb'elle, 796004 (Box 25)
  - Reciprocity, 796003 (Box 25)
  - Red, 796002 (Box 25)
  - Reduced to Clear, 796001 (Box 25)
  - Reflections on Women in Prison, 796000 (Box 25)
  - Refugee, 795999 (Box 25)
  - Reject, 795998 (Box 25)
  - Rejection, 795997 (Box 25)
  - Replica, 795996 (Box 25)
  - (Re)Sisters, 795995 (Box 25)
  - Restoring Harmony, 795994 (Box 25)
  - Retort, 795993 (Box 26)
  - Revolver, Dauphin, 795992 (Box 26)
  - Rina Zine, 795991 (Box 26)
  - Riot Grrrl Life, 795990 (Box 26)
  - Riot Grrrl NYC, 795989 (Box 26)
  - Riot Grrrl Press Flyer, 795988 (Box 26)
  - Riveter, 795987 (Box 26)
  - Robots 1 Humans 0, 795986 (Box 26)
  - Rockgirl, 795985 (Box 26)
  - Rock Star with Purses: a Story About a Girl, 795984 (Box 26)
  - Rocket Queen, 795983 (Box 26)
  - Roller Derby (2 Folders), 795982 (Box 26)
  - Room 258, 795981 (Box 26)
  - Root (3 Folders), 795980 (Box 26)
  - Roots and Wings, 795979 (Box 26)
  - Roses, 795978 (Box 26)
  - Rotten Apples, 795977 (Box 26)
  - Rotting From the Inside, 795976 (Box 26)
  - Ruby Fruit Manifesto, 795975 (Box 26)
  - Rug Burn, 795974 (Box 26)
  - Safe, Legal Abortion Access, 795973 (Box 26)
  - Said It, 795972 (Box 26)
  - Salt and Slush, 795971 (Box 26)
  - Sanity Sux, 795970 (Box 26)
  - Say the Word, 795969 (Box 26)
  - "Scarlet 'A'", 795968 (Box 26)
  - Scram Magazine (5 Folders), 795967 (Box 27)
  - Seattle - Left Bank Books, 795966 (Box 27)
  - The Secret and Romantic Life of Spence, 795965 (Box 27)
  - The Secret Life of Vidalia Sparkle, 795964 (Box 27)
  - Self-Portraits (2 Folders), 795963 (Box 27)
  - Self-Titled, 795962 (Box 27)
  - Selling the Drama, 795961 (Box 27)
  - Semi Bold (2 Folders), 795960 (Box 27)
  - Set on Freedom, 795959 (Box 27)
  - Seventh Grade, 795958 (Box 28)
  - Shari Vari, 795957 (Box 28)
  - She, 795956 (Box 28)
  - She Made This, 795955 (Box 28)
  - Shithole, 795954 (Box 28)
  - Shocking Pink, 795953 (Box 28)
  - shortandqueer (4 Folders), 795952 (Box 28)
  - Shotgun Wedding, 795951 (Box 28)
  - Shotgun Seamstress, 795950 (Box 28)
  - Show and Tell, 795949 (Box 28)
  - Sidetracks of Consciousness, 795948 (Box 28)
  - Simplified Skeleton, 795947 (Box 28)
  - The Skandha Skandhal, 795946 (Box 28)
  - Skills, 795945 (Box 28)
  - Skin on Skin, 795944 (Box 28)
  - Skinned Heart, 795943 (Box 28)
  - Sky Flying By, 795942 (Box 28)
  - Slaves to the Needles, 795941 (Box 28)
  - Slip Into Something Human (2 Folders), 795940 (Box 28)
  - Smells Like Burning Angst, 795939 (Box 28)
  - Smile For Me, 795938 (Box 28)
  - Smitten Kitten Zine Distro, 795937 (Box 28)
  - Sneer (viva la morte de l'ete), 795936 (Box 28)
  - Soap, 795935 (Box 28)
  - Soggy Birds Don't Sing, 795934 (Box 28)
  - Sojourner, 795933 (Box 28)
  - Soiled Princess, 795932 (Box 28)
  - Soliloquy, 795931 (Box 28)
  - So Maybe Niza Mai, 795930 (Box 28)
  - Some Misplaced Joan of Arc, 795929 (Box 29)
  - Someone [Hearts] Me in Ohio, 795928 (Box 29)
  - Something, In My Pocket, 795927 (Box 29)
  - Sometimes I Just Want to Write on Walls, 795926 (Box 29)
  - Somnabulist, 795925 (Box 29)
  - Songs of the Day Shift Foreman: Journal of a Rainforest Witch, 795924 (Box 29)
  - Soul Fish, 795923 (Box 29)
  - Sour Puss (2 Folders), 795922 (Box 29)
  - South Chicago ABC Zine Distro, 795921 (Box 29)
  - Space Craft Convention, 795920 (Box 29)
  - Speak-Easy/The Travel Issue, 795919 (Box 29)
  - The Special People's Club (2 Folders), 795918 (Box 29)
  - Speculum Veritas, 795917 (Box 29)
  - Spider Stompin', 795916 (Box 29)
  - A Spin-Off of Marvel's Fantastic Four, 795915 (Box 29)
  - Squid, 795914 (Box 29)
  - Squirrel Haiku Zine, 795913 (Box 29)
  - Stab and Root (2 Folders), 795912 (Box 29)
  - Standing Ovations for Sleeping Children, 795911 (Box 29)
  - Star Gang, 795910 (Box 29)
  - Stay Aware, 795909 (Box 29)
  - Staying Gold, 795908 (Box 29)
  - Steve Albini Thinks We Suck, 795907 (Box 29)
  - Stick 'em Up, 795906 (Box 29)
  - St. Ink, 795905 (Box 29)
  - Stitch Witchery, 795904 (Box 29)
  - Sub Rosa, 795903 (Box 29)
  - Suburban Blight (2 Folders), 795902 (Box 29)
  - Sunnyside Down, 795901 (Box 29)
  - Supermarket Super Model, 795900 (Box 29)
  - Support (2 Folders), 795899 (Box 30)
  - Surf's Up, 795898 (Box 30)
  - Survival Guide for Her Repellant, 795897 (Box 30)
  - Suzann Gage, 795896 (Box 30)
  - Swearing at Traffic Keeps Me Sane, 795895 (Box 30)
  - Sweet Valley Zine, 795894 (Box 30)
  - The System, 795893 (Box 30)
  - Take Back Your Life: A Wimmin's Guide to Alternative Health Care, 795892 (Box 30)
  - Take Care, 795891 (Box 30)
  - The Tale of Dick Shellfull, 795890 (Box 30)
  - Tazewell's Favorite Eccentric, 795889 (Box 30)
  - Teacup (2 Folders), 795888 (Box 30)
  - The Tea Party, 795887 (Box 30)
  - Technological Disadvantages, 795886 (Box 30)
  - Teen Voices, 795885 (Box 30)
  - Teen Sex, 795884 (Box 30)
  - Telegram Ma'am (2 Folders), 795883 (Box 30)
  - Television is Evil, 795882 (Box 30)
  - Temple of Sting (2 Folders), 795881 (Box 30)
  - Tenacious (4 Folders), 795880 (Box 30)
  - A Tenderness So Painful I Thought My Heart Would Burst, 795879 (Box 30)
  - A Terrible, Horrible, No Good, Very Bad, Life, 795878 (Box 30)
  - Therapeutic Insurrection: Radiocal Healthcare Theory, 795877 (Box 31)
  - Thermal Jerk Poetry, 795876 (Box 31)
  - These Here Are Crazy Times, 795875 (Box 31)
  - Thick Farmgirl Legs, 795874 (Box 31)
  - Things That Don't Make Sense, 795873 (Box 31)
  - Thirdspace, 795872 (Box 31)
  - This Bunch of Flowers, 795871 (Box 31)
  - This is Me Using My Choice/An Anthology of Women's Abortion Stories, 795870 (Box 31)
  - This is Before You Were Born, 795869 (Box 31)
  - This Way Out, 795868 (Box 31)
  - Thorn, 795867 (Box 31)
  - The Three Musketeers, 795866 (Box 31)
  - Thrift Poetic Arts Journal, 795865 (Box 31)
  - Thrift Score, 795864 (Box 31)
  - Thrill!, 795863 (Box 31)
  - Throwing Energy Around, 795862 (Box 31)
  - Tic Tic, 795861 (Box 31)
  - Tight Pants, 795860 (Box 31)
  - Time To Disappear, 795859 (Box 31)
  - To Be A Problem--Alexis Gumbs, 795858 (Box 31)
  - Toilet Paper Zine, 795857 (Box 31)
  - Toward, 795856 (Box 31)
  - Transit, 795855 (Box 31)
  - Translucid Distortion, 795854 (Box 31)
  - The Trap or Lion-Eater, 795853 (Box 31)
  - Trash, 795852 (Box 31)
  - Trash or Treasure, 795851 (Box 31)
  - Tropical Depression, 795850 (Box 31)
  - Truckface (2 Folders), 795849 (Box 31)
  - Truckface, 795848 (Box 32)
  - Tuff Town, 795847 (Box 32)
  - Tuhia: A Manifesto, 795846 (Box 32)
  - Turn, 795845 (Box 32)
  - The Twin Survey, 795844 (Box 32)
  - A Two-Bean Theory, 795843 (Box 32)
  - Two Left Feet, 795842 (Box 32)
  - "T" Word: Pass the Mission, 795841 (Box 32)
  - Typecast Typecrazy, 795840 (Box 32)
  - The Underdog, 795839 (Box 32)
  - Underpants, 795838 (Box 32)
  - Ungrateful White-Black Girl, 795837 (Box 32)
  - University (2 Folders), 795836 (Box 32)
  - [untitled] (3 Folders), 795835 (Box 32)
  - The Urban Herbalist, 795834 (Box 32)
  - U.S. Keep Your Hands Off Assata, 795833 (Box 32)
  - Valley Girl, 795832 (Box 32)
  - Vampire Costume Store, 795831 (Box 32)
  - Vegetable Vegetable Mineral, 795830 (Box 32)
  - Vena Cava, 795829 (Box 32)
  - Venus, 795828 (Box 32)
  - Violent Crimes, 795827 (Box 32)
  - Vitamina, Minerals, and Mental Health, 795826 (Box 32)
  - Vitophobia, 795825 (Box 33)
  - Viva La Marines, 795824 (Box 33)
  - Vodka and My Dog, 795823 (Box 33)
  - Voluntary Transaction, 795822 (Box 33)
  - Vortex, 795821 (Box 33)
  - V-Reject, 795820 (Box 33)
  - Waffles, 795819 (Box 33)
  - Wait 5 Minutes, It Will Change, 795818 (Box 33)
  - Walking in L.A., 795817 (Box 33)
  - Walk On, 795816 (Box 33)
  - The Way Things Used to Be, 795815 (Box 33)
  - We Are Warriors: a Comp. About Anti-Oppression, 795814 (Box 33)
  - We Carry Each Other, 795813 (Box 33)
  - We Said We Didn't Have a Life: Here's Proof, 795812 (Box 33)
  - "We Should": A Selective Guide to Chicago, 795811 (Box 33)
  - What Did You Buy Today? (3 Folders), 795810 (Box 33)
  - What I Saw From Where I Stood, 795809 (Box 33)
  - What It Is, 795808 (Box 33)
  - What We Want: An Anarcha-Feminist Perspective of Feminism, 795807 (Box 34)
  - Wheatpaste, 795806 (Box 34)
  - White Blackbirds (2 Folders), 795805 (Box 34)
  - White Boy, 795804 (Box 34)
  - White Elephants, 795803 (Box 34)
  - Whizzbanger Catalog, 795802 (Box 34)
  - Who Is This Woman?, 795801 (Box 34)
  - Whose Feminism Is It Anyway?, 795800 (Box 34)
  - Wicked, 795799 (Box 34)
  - Wiglet, 795798 (Box 34)
  - Wild Honey Pie, 795797 (Box 34)
  - Wishing For My Star, 795796 (Box 34)
  - Witches, Midwives, and Nurses, 795795 (Box 34)
  - With Love, From Me, To You, 795794 (Box 34)
  - Women and Imprisonment in the United States (2 Folders), 795793 (Box 34)
  - Women are in Prison (2 Folders), 795792 (Box 34)
  - Women For Freedom, 795791 (Box 34)
  - Women's Herstory, 795790 (Box 34)
  - Women's Self-Defense Stories: Strategies of Survival, 795789 (Box 34)
  - Womyn/Wimmin Who Masturbate, 795788 (Box 34)
  - Word and Image, 795787 (Box 34)
  - Word Salad, 795786 (Box 34)
  - Work, 795785 (Box 34)
  - Work/Play Magazine, 795784 (Box 34)
  - Woven, 795783 (Box 34)
  - Writer's Exchange, 795782 (Box 34)
  - Xerox Debt, 795781 (Box 34)
  - Xploited Zine, 795780 (Box 34)
  - Xtra Tuf, 795779 (Box 34)
  - Year 23 Postcard, 795778 (Box 35)
  - Yesterday's Fishwrap Could Be Today's Oracle, 795777 (Box 35)
  - You, 795776 (Box 35)
  - You Can Work Any Hundred Hours..., 795775 (Box 35)
  - You Live For the Fight When That's All You Got, 795774 (Box 35)
  - Your Pretty Face is Going to Hell, 795773 (Box 35)
  - Yuck!, 795772 (Box 35)
  - Zeniths Integrate Nouveau Effervescences: A DIY Resource, 795771 (Box 35)
  - Zigzaggery, 795770 (Box 35)
  - Zine Conference: Connecting Counterculture, 795769 (Box 35)
  - Zine Librarian Zine (3 Folders), 795768 (Box 35)
  - Zine Making: An Introduction, 795767 (Box 35)
  - Zinetopia, 795766 (Box 35)
  - Zineworks Coachella Handbook, 795765 (Box 35)
  - Zine World (4 Folders), 795764 (Box 35)
  - Zipped, 795763 (Box 35)
  - Zipper, 795762 (Box 35)
  - Zombie Freak-out, 795761 (Box 35)
  - Zuzu and the Baby Catcher, 795760 (Box 35)
- Accession (2013-0208), 1992-2013; 870028; 2.5 Linear Feet; 4 boxes
  - Adventures in Menstruating, 2006-2011, 870029; 4 Issues: 2, 4-6: Sheffield, UK (Box 36)
  - Adventures with Riot Grrrill, 2011, 870050; 1 issue (Box 36)
  - All I Want is Everything, 2010-2012, 870051; 3 Issues: 1-3: Clearwater, FL (Box 36)
  - All That We Can Do, 2001, 870052; 1 issue (Box 36)
  - The Archivalist, 2010, 870053; 1 issue: 5: Richmond, VA (Box 36)
  - Bay State Badass, 2011-2012, 870054; 2 Issues: 1-2: Cambridge, MA (Box 36)
  - Betrayal, 870055; 1 issue (Box 36)
  - Big Cat Parade!, 2010, 870056; 1 issue (Box 36)
  - Black Lesbians in the 1970s and Before, 2010, 870057; 1 Issue: April 2010: New York (Box 36)
  - The Borough is My Library, 2009-2011, 870058; 3 Issues: 1-3: Brooklyn, NY (Box 36)
  - Brownie Kids, 870059; 1 issue (Box 36)
  - A Call to Arms, 870060; 1 issue (Box 36)
  - "Canning" Capitalist Agribusiness: A Simple How-To Guide to Canning Your Produce, 870061; 1 issue (Box 36)
  - Chingozine, 2012, 870062; 1 issue: 1: San Antonio, TX (Box 36)
  - Consent, 870063; 1 issue (Box 36)
  - Cranky Pants, 2010, 870064; 1 issue: 2010 (Box 36)
  - Culture Slut, 2011, 870065; 1 issue: 25 (Box 36)
  - danger third rail is electric, 2002, 870066; 3 issues: 1-3: New York, NY (Box 36)
  - Deafula, 2011, 870067; 1 issue: 2 (Box 36)
  - Dig Deep, 2010-2011, 870068 (Box 36)
  - Dirty Diamonds, 2011, 870069; 1 issue: Summer 2011 (Box 36)
  - Doris, 2009-2012, 870070; 4 issues: 26-29: Akron, OH (Box 36)
  - Draw Blood, 2003-2004, 870071; 1 issue: 2003-04: Oakland, CA (Box 36)
  - Echo! Echo!, 2007-2011, 870072; 2 issues: 4-5 (Box 36)
  - Enabled him, 870073; 1 issue (Box 36)
  - Falling without a net, 2002, 870074; 1 issue: 2002 (Box 36)
  - Fat Girl, 1994-1997, 870075; 7 issues: 1-7: San Francisco, CA (Box 37)
  - Fat Girl Breakdown, 870076; 1 issue (Box 37)
  - Fat-tastic, 870077; 1 issue (Box 37)
  - fatty fashions, 2006, 870078; 1 issue: May 2006 (Box 37)
  - The F-Bomb, 2011, 870079; 1 issue: Spring 2011 (Box 37)
  - Feel Free to Stare, 870080; 1 issue (Box 37)
  - Feels Like Friday, 2005, 870081; 1 issue: 1: St Johns Park, AU (Box 37)
  - Feminism 101, 870082; 1 issue (Box 37)
  - Femme a barbe, 870083; 1 issue: 3 (Box 37)
  - Filling the Void, 870084; 1 issue: Athens, OH (Box 37)
  - Fit, 2011, 870085; 1 issue: Nov. 2011 (Box 37)
  - Foxfire, 870086; 1 issue: 1: Santa Cruz, CA (Box 37)
  - Functionally Ill, 870087; 1 issue: 10: Sacramento, CA (Box 37)
  - Future Tense, 2012, 870088; 1 issue: 2012: Brooklyn, NY (Box 37)
  - Gay Kid, 1993-2011, 870089; 3 issues: 1-3 (Box 37)
  - Gendered Space, 870090; 1 issue: vol. 1 (Box 37)
  - Get Fit for the Pit, 2011, 870091; 1 issue: Richmond, VA (Box 37)
  - Grow Up!, 2011, 870092; 1 issue: 2011: Grand Rapids, MI (Box 37)
  - Hairstory, 870093; 1 issue (Box 37)
  - H.F. Johnson Gallery of Art Zines, 2012, 870094; 9 issues: Kenosha, WI (Box 37)
  - Hi-Yay to Hell/Brazen Hussy, 870095; 1 issue: 2/6: Chattanooga, TN (Box 37)
  - Homos in Herstory, 870096; 2 issues (Box 37)
  - An interview transcription between Benjam Ben-Eliezer and Arin Ahmed Conducted in Israel June 9, 2002, 870097; 1 Issue: July/August 2003 (Box 37)
  - Kit-Cat, 870098; 1 issue (Box 37)
  - Leaving Room for the Im/Possibility of Unicorns, 870099; 1 issue (Box 37)
  - Letters to Self, 870100; 1 issue: New York, NY (Box 37)
  - Life and Times of Butch Dykes, 2009-2011, 870101; 5 issues (Box 37)
  - Life, Death, Love, & "All of the Above", 2011, 870102; 1 issue: 2011 (Box 37)
  - Lowest East Side Librarian, 2011, 870103; 1 issue: Sept. 2011: New York, NY (Box 38)
  - Lower East Side Librarian & Friends Menstruate, 2012, 870104; 1 issue: April 2012: New York, NY (Box 38, Box 37)
  - The Mai Tai Exotic Cocktail Guide, 2003, 870105; 1 issue: 10: Montreal, QC (Box 38)
  - Mal Life, 1992, 870106; 1 issue: 22: Phoenix, AZ (Box 38)
  - Mildly Irritating, 2009, 870107; 1 issue: 2009 (Box 38)
  - Miss Sequential's Sketchbook, 2012, 870108; 1 issue: 5: Cambridge, MA (Box 38)
  - Motor City Kitty, 2011, 870109; 2 issues: 17-18: Kent, OH (Box 38)
  - My Feminist Friends, 2011, 870110; 1 issue: May, 2011: New York, NY (Box 38)
  - Nega-Tiva, 870111; 1 issue: 1: Chicago, IL (Box 38)
  - No Mas Para Angelina, 2005, 870112; 1 issue: Aug. 2005 (Box 38)
  - Nothing Rhymes, 2009, 870113; 1 issue: 5: Providence, RI (Box 38)
  - Not "queer" as in "radical", 2012, 870114; 1 issue: Feb. 2012 (Box 38)
  - Now We're Cooking With Food, 870115; 1 issue: Toronto, ON (Box 38)
  - Our Struggling Identity, 870116; 1 issue: Chicago, IL (Box 38)
  - Outsiders: Zines, Samizdat & Alternate Publishing, 2013, 870117; 1 issue: April, 2013, Chicago, IL (Box 38)
  - Phoenix Fire, 2005, 870118; 1 issue: 2005 (Box 38)
  - Pinch Kid, 870119; 1 issue: Montreal, QC (Box 38)
  - Pink Toes and Beast, 2011-2012, 870120; 2 issues: Cleveland, OH (Box 38)
  - Problem? Solution!, 870121; 1 issue (Box 38)
  - Psucho Moto zine, 870122; 1 issue: 21 (Box 38)
  - The Queen in the Dance Party and other stories, 2010, 870123; 1 issue: 2010: Beijing, China (Box 38)
  - Rav, 870124; 3 issues: 3, 5-6: Providence, RI (Box 38)
  - Reimagining Queer Community: A Perzine, 2011, 870125; 1 issue: July 2011: Baltimore, MD (Box 38)
  - Riot Grrrl Press, 1993, 870126; 1 issue: 1993: Arlington, VA (Box 38)
  - Riot Librarrrian, 2002, 870127; 1 issue: Winter 2002: Chicago, IL (Box 38)
  - Roam (for the life of little things), 2012, 870128; 1 issue: 3: Green Bay, WI (Box 38)
  - Sagari, 870129; 1 issue: Providence, RI (Box 39)
  - Sassyfrass Circus, 2010-2011, 870130; 2 issues: 6-7: Washington, DC (Box 39)
  - Self Defense for Pregnant Women, 870131; 1 issue: Richmond, VA (Box 39)
  - Shakespeare's Sister, 1998, 870132; 1 issue: Richmond, VA (Box 39)
  - She Magazine, 2010, 870133; 1 issue: 1.1 (Box 39)
  - She Must Be Having a Bad Day, 870134; 1 issue: 2 (Box 39)
  - So, this is what it's come to ..., 870135; 1 issue (Box 39)
  - Star Cinema, 870136; 1 issue (Box 39)
  - Sticker Sisters, 870137; 1 issue: Takoma Park, MD (Box 39)
  - Strife, 1996-1997, 870138; 4 issues: 1-4: Birmingham, AL (Box 39)
  - Suggestion Box, 2006-2011, 870139; 8 issues: 1-6, Tales, Confessions (Box 39)
  - Teaching Info Literacy with Zines, 2011, 870140; 1 issue: July 2011: Iowa City, IA (Box 39)
  - Twins for Sale, 2011, 870141; 1 issue: 2011 (Box 39)
  - Twins, 2012, 870142; 1 issue: 2012 (Box 39)
  - Vagina: the Zine, 2013, 870143; 1 issue: 7: Austin, TX (Box 39)
  - Vidya, 2003, 870144; 1 issue: 1 (Box 39)
  - Welcome to the Bend, 2010, 870145; 1 issue: 1: Bend, OR (Box 39)
  - When You Read This You'll Know Who You Are, 1991, 870146; 1 issue: 1991 (Box 39)
  - Woman Alone, 870147; 1 issue: Ontario (Box 39)
  - Works Cited, 2007, 870148; 1 issue: July 2007: Champaign, IL (Box 39)
  - xZINECOREx: An Introduction, 2013, 870149; 1 issue: April, 2013 (Box 39)
  - Zine Librarian Zine, 2003, 870150; 1 issue: April 2013 (Box 39)
  - Zine Libs, 2012, 870151; 1 issue: 1+2: Brookly, NY (Box 39)
  - Zoos Blues, 870152; 1 issue (Box 39)
- Accession (2014-0159), 1992-2014; 1.5 Linear Feet; 2 boxes
  - (Correspondence etc.) (Box 40)
  - About My Body (Because You Always Ask) (Box 40)
  - A Brief History of the Iowa Abortion Access Fund (Box 40)
  - "Africa" ... Messages to Black Women (Box 40)
  - A Smidgeon of Ecofeminism (Box 40)
  - ANAlog (Box 40)
  - An Ire Adrift Songbook (Box 40)
  - Are You There, God? It's Me, Menopause (Box 40)
  - Ask First! (Box 40)
  - Beware Rape Culture (Box 40)
  - Beyond the Research Paper (Box 40)
  - Birds Birds Birds (Box 40)
  - Big Fish (Box 40)
  - Black Hole (Box 40)
  - Bold Life (Box 40)
  - Book (Box 40)
  - Brokenpencil (Box 40)
  - Bubby (Box 40)
  - C. Exigua (Box 40)
  - Camellia (Box 40)
  - Choose Your Own Consensual Adventure (Box 40)
  - The Cleveland Review (Box 40)
  - Close to My Heart (Box 40)
  - Coloring Outside the Kitchen (Box 40)
  - Cuke + Sew (Box 40)
  - Curioddity (Box 40)
  - Dangerous Damsels (Box 40)
  - Dawa Dawa (Box 40)
  - Deathscort (Box 40)
  - Dirty Thoughts in Church (Box 40)
  - Dislocations (Box 40)
  - Do It Yourself Gynecological Exam (Box 40)
  - Don't Be a Dick (Box 40)
  - Doris (Box 40)
  - Dream Protocols (Box 40)
  - The Dwarves of Dahlstrom! (Box 40)
  - Eclipse (Box 40)
  - 11x30 (Box 40)
  - Empowering Women: A Tale of Two Generations (Box 40)
  - Exceeding the Self (Box 40)
  - Fat (Box 40)
  - Fat-Tastic! (Box 40)
  - Flack (Box 40)
  - Frankie Comics (Box 40)
  - Free to Fight! (Box 40)
  - Free Voices (Box 40)
  - Frig That (Box 40)
  - From the Punked Out Files of the Queer Zine Archive Project (Box 40)
  - Fuck Me: A Zine on Gender Violence at Duke University (Box 40)
  - Gender Oppression, Abuse, Violence (Box 40)
  - Ghost Lungs (Box 40)
  - Girl-Boy (Box 40)
  - Giving Up the Ghost (Box 40)
  - Good Things to Eat From the Rubenstein Library Test Kitchen (Box 40)
  - The Gourd (Box 40)
  - GQ Tales (Box 40)
  - Harlot, RN (Box 41)
  - Her Creative Pursuits (Box 40)
  - hoax (Box 40)
  - Hold Tight (Box 40)
  - Homos in Herstory: 1970s Edition (Box 40)
  - Illusion (Box 40)
  - Impermanent Glamour (Box 40)
  - In Defense of Giving Up On a New City (Box 40)
  - Indefinite Space (Box 40)
  - In the Jaws of the Monster (Box 40)
  - It's Down to This (Box 40)
  - The Jesus Plates (Box 40)
  - Lasterday (Box 40)
  - Letter to a Gender Rebel (Box 40)
  - Limbo (Box 40)
  - Liontamer (Box 40)
  - Made-Up: A Book for Coloring (Box 41)
  - Mad World Anthology (Box 41)
  - Making Fun of Us (Box 41)
  - Mala Leche (Box 41)
  - Margarine (Box 41)
  - Mend My Dress (Box 41)
  - Me Party (Box 41)
  - Mineshaft (Box 41)
  - Mixed Media (Box 41)
  - Motor City Kitty (Box 41)
  - Multispecies Bodysnatching (Box 41)
  - Musings of a #LonelyFeminist (Box 41)
  - My Feminist Friends (Box 41)
  - My Life in Zines (Box 41)
  - Nashville Transit (Box 41)
  - Neither Doll Houses Nor Tree Houses (Box 41)
  - No Better Than Apples (Box 41)
  - No Gods, No Dungeon Masters (Box 41)
  - Notes From An Afro-Genderqueer Philosophactivist (Box 41)
  - Nonfiction Liberal Omph (Box 41)
  - Not 'Queer' as in Radical But 'Lesbian' as in Fuck You! (Box 41)
  - Olympia's 5th Annual Sex Workers' Art Show (Box 41)
  - The Olympia Sex Conference Zine (Box 41)
  - Omnific (Box 41)
  - On Being Hard Femme (Box 41)
  - Our Own Response (Box 41)
  - Owl Scat (Box 41)
  - Philosophactivism (Box 41)
  - Pinch Kid (Box 41)
  - Putting Ya Face On (Box 41)
  - Postcards for Pansies (Box 41)
  - Privacy (Box 41)
  - Queering Herbalism (Box 41)
  - Quiet Riot (Box 41)
  - Quitter (Box 41)
  - Rad Dad (Box 41)
  - Rainbow in the Dark (Box 41)
  - Reimagining Queer Community (Box 41)
  - The Reluctant Ghost Hunter (Box 41)
  - ReVision: Zines and Collage (Box 41)
  - Rot (Box 41)
  - Rumpy Pumpy (Box 41)
  - Scan Omit Loop (Box 41)
  - Sea Sponge Revolution (Box 41)
  - Second to None: Queer + Trans Chicago Voices (Box 41)
  - See No Speak No Hear No (Box 41)
  - Self Defense for Pregnant Women (Box 41)
  - Self Esteem (Box 41)
  - Sex Letters (Box 41)
  - #Social Media Anxieties (Box 41)
  - Some Helpful Information on Domestic Violence for Radical Communities (Box 41)
  - The Southern Libertarian Messenger (Box 41)
  - Spider Teeth (Box 41)
  - Still Beating Heart (Box 41)
  - Strange Growths (Box 41)
  - Strange Highways (Box 41)
  - Study: A Zine About Surviving Graduate School (Box 41)
  - Sugar Needle (Box 41)
  - Taking Risks (Box 41)
  - Tax Watch (Box 41)
  - Teaching Consent to My Kitten (Box 41)
  - Telegram (Box 41)
  - This Year in Numbers (Box 41)
  - Thou Shalt Not Talk About the White Boys Club (Box 41)
  - Touchpoint (Box 41)
  - Tourists of the Heart (Box 41)
  - Trans Canada (Box 41)
  - Trans-ient Life Form (Box 41)
  - Trans Media Revolution (Box 41)
  - The 28-Day Grace Kelly Diet (Box 41)
  - 23 (Box 41)
  - Ultimate Voyages Through Language and History (Box 41)
  - Undead/Reliving (Box 41)
  - Undress (Box 41)
  - Unzipped: The Duke Journal of Gender and Sexuality (Box 41)
  - Urbanus (Box 41)
  - Us Amazonians: A Kirsty MacColl Fanzine (Box 41)
  - V Emotional (Box 41)